cre8asiteforums.com 2009-08-05

# Privacy Policy - Cre8asite Forums

## Terms of Use

This statement covers all of the Cre8asiteForums sites (Blog, Directory, Forums, and any page contained within the Cre8pc or Cre8asite family of web sites) and any associated content including email, private messages, forum feeds and RSS.

Please read this statement carefully before using proceeding to access any of the Cre8asiteForums sites. Your use of the Cre8asiteForums sites indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

Cre8pc.com and Cre8asiteForums.com are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.

**ALL Text Links inside the forums and any sponsored links are not crawlable by any search engine, with "nofollow" or proprietary "url scrambling".**

## Basic Confidentiality Policy

It is Cre8pc/Cre8asiteforums's policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and email address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, any **personal** information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to reply to your request or to handle your complaint).

You are solely responsible for whatever personal or private information you post in Cre8asiteForums. This includes any URLs, address, phone number or email address added to your signature line or within Comments or a forums post.

**Cre8asiteForums is actively crawled and indexed by the major search engines, including every post. Be careful what information you place in your posts.**

We do not keep records of your passwords and cannot retrieve it for you if should lose your password.

## No Release of Information to Third Parties

Personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information, such as networking with other businesses, or allowing Cre8pc.com to recommend your services for promotional purposes, at your request. _There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties_.

Please be advised that Cre8asiteforums is subject to email harvesters, for which we have no control over. Again, do not post your email address to avoid being picked up by harvesting software.

On occasion, we learn of someone receiving unsolicited email from a company claiming to have found them via Cre8asiteForums. Please report to Cre8pc/Cre8asiteforums Administrators these violations of your privacy, but also remember a public forum is often where marketers seek potential customers.

## No Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information

Our computer is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the home server of visitors. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our sites, unless purposely placed in your Profile at Cre8asiteForums.com.

No personal information is collected. Ever. In addition, our web sites track information about the visits to our web sites. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, such as our advertisers, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

**Cre8pc.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of participants in its various programs, affiliate links, or any off-site URL. Please refer to our Terms and Conditions.**

## Reciprocal Links

It is our policy to not link to "link farm" pages. Automated link requests are not accepted or reciprocated. We do not exchange links or entertain link requests of any type.

\-- 

Established January 10, 1998

Last updated December 2, 2007
